which real life cheat codes do you know? To save time I sometimes pretend that I'm the dumb one
that may have made the mistake to avoid the... hole it wasn't my fault conversation. It allows me
to take blame and move on to the solution when the solution is all I care about. I don't care
who's at fault I just need it fixed. If you sleep in the same bed as you're so, don't share a blanket.
Each person should have their own blanket. Whichever one it is that helps them sleep the best.
Colder or warmer. Comforter versus quilt etc. You'll sleep so much better.
Cutting out daily drinks with sugar like sodas or frappuccinos really helps with weight loss if you
do nothing else. If you're stuck trying to finish or even start something like studying or
working on an assignment. Take a piece of paper and write down your thoughts or anything you're
worried about. Once you've got them all. Put the paper away and you should feel more relaxed to
finish what you were doing. Helps a lot of procrastination and anxiety. Don't wait until the person is
dead to tell them how you feel. Whether it's good, bad or indifferent. Once they are gone, it's too
late and a huge waste of time obsessing over someone who is no longer here.